youngmoney.com 2011-08-24

# Privacy Statement

This website (“Company Website”) is operated by Young Money Media, LLC (“Company”) and this policy applies to all websites owned, operated, controlled and otherwise made available by Company, its affiliates and supported organizations (including, but not limited to, mirrored, co-branded and successor sites). Our office address is:

Young Money Media, LLC  
10950 Gilroy Road  
Suite D  
Hunt Valley, MD 21031  
United States of America  
We may be reached via [email](mailto:admin@youngmoney.com).

Introduction

Company respects the privacy and security of your personal information. The following privacy policy describes the information we collect, how we use it and what rights you have to it. By using this Company Website, you acknowledge and agree to the terms and conditions of this Website Privacy Policy Statement (“Privacy Policy”). If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use this Company Website.

We reserve the right to change or modify our privacy practices that are described herein from time to time simply by posting a revised Privacy Policy on this Company Website. Any such change shall be effective immediately upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on this Company Website. We reserve the right to make the revised or changed Privacy Policy effective for information we already have about you, as well as any information we receive in the future. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy practices.

Privacy Policy

Like many websites, we gather information about how visitors use this Company Website. In general, you can visit many of the web pages on this Company Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We, however, may track your Internet Protocol (IP) address and other anonymous information from your web browser for trends and statistics (including, but not limited to, browser version, pages requested and pages visited), but you will remain anonymous unless you provide us with personal information during your visit to this Company Website or during an earlier or subsequent visit and we are able to link your IP address between your current visit and one of these other visits.

We also work with service providers who use tracking technologies to serve ads across the Internet or track email communication response rates on our behalf. These companies may collect personal information about your visits to this Company Website and your interaction with our communications, including advertising.

In addition to anonymous information, we also collect personal information from you at this Company Website when you voluntarily submit it to us. We request personal information from you (which may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, gender, year of birth, and when necessary, credit account information) when you:

  * Complete a request, registration, survey, application or other form;
  * Request a product or service from us or from one of our vendors, suppliers or other agents;
  * Sign-up to receive email newsletters or other correspondence;
  * Submit materials to this Website;
  * Participate in a promotion, contest, sweepstakes or similar promotional activity;
  * Request materials from us; and/or
  * Request e-mail, fax, mail or telephone support or services.

We also collect information about your activities on and through this Company Website from other third parties.

You may choose not to provide us with any personal information. In such event, you can still access and use many portions of this Company Website; however, you will not be able to access and use those portions of this Company Website or the services available on or through this Company Website that require your personal information.

Using Information

We may use the information we collect to:

  * Customize and/or personalize your communications, surfing, viewing, and user experience; 
  * Better respond to your customer service inquiries;
  * Communicate with you about your account information, or customer service needs;
  * Communicate with you about our services and events, and for other promotional purposes;
  * Improve our service;
  * Administer contests, promotions, surveys or other website features;
  * Provide technical support to you; and
  * Perform any other lawful acts except for those acts expressly prohibited by the terms and conditions set forth herein.

Sharing Information

Except as expressly set forth herein, we do not loan, give away, sell, distribute or rent your personal information to any third party.

We will disclose your personal information to third parties if you have previously consented to such disclosures and in special circumstances, including, but not limited to, the sale of Company or any portion thereof; during the due diligence in connection with a potential sale of Company or any portion thereof; during any bankruptcy, insolvency or liquidation of Company; or in other similar circumstances.

For the purpose of fulfilling our mission and providing you with certain services and products and to process your requests, purchases, and payments, we may disclose your personal information to one or more of our affiliates, service providers or other third parties who are assisting Company in performing such services. Without limiting the foregoing, these third parties may provide Company with payment processing, shipping, data management, email distribution, live text chat, email response, market research, information analysis, and promotions management services. We provide such parties with the personal information they need to perform their respective services and we use commercially reasonable efforts to require them to safeguard your personal information and limit their use of it.

We also may provide your personal information to other Company-affiliated companies which may be outside the United States, and who may use your personal information for any legal purposes whatsoever.

We also may disclose personal information about you upon request by the government; in response to a court order; when required by law or when we believe in good faith is required by law; to enforce our Privacy Policy, terms and conditions or other agreements and polices on this Company Website; upon your request; or to contact, identify or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with our or others’ rights or property including, but not limited to, claims for infringement of intellectual property, invasions of privacy or situations involving threats or alleged threats to the physical safety of a person’s property. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing purposes.

We may also provide aggregated, non-personally identifiable information to third parties for any legal purposes whatsoever.

Protecting Your Information

We use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard and secure your personal information while stored on our computer systems. We use a variety of industry standard security measures, including encryption and authentication tools, to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information. Your personal information is stored behind industry standard firewalls and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who are authorized to access such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. Regardless of these efforts by us, no system connected to the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

We use commercially reasonable effort to safeguard and secure the transmission of your personal information from your computer to our computers. When you access your personal information or place orders, we offer the use of a secure server. To the extent you select the secure server method or your browser supports such functionality, all credit account information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Regardless of these efforts by us, no data transmission over the public Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

Cookies and Pixel Tags

This Company Website uses cookies. A cookie is a small, removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies allow you to place an order on this Company Website and allow us to enhance, facilitate and personalize your online surfing and user experience. For example, we use cookies to:

  * Recognize you when you return to this Company Website;
  * Present relevant content to you when you visit this Company Website;
  * Analyze visitor behavior; and
  * Facilitate other similar types of activities.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your web browser settings. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your visit to this Company Website more efficient and enjoyable, and in some cases, some of our services will not function or will function with limited capability. 

We also use pixel tags- tiny graphic images- to help us analyze your online behavior and information about visitors to this Company Website and our customers. Pixel tags also allow us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us. 

Tell a Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Company collects the email address of your friend for the sole purpose of automatically sending the friend an email inviting them to visit the site but does not store this information.

Children’s Online Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. This Company Website is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under the age of 13, and we have made commercially reasonable efforts to design this Company Website to prevent our knowing acceptance of any such information.

It is possible that by fraud, deception or error, we may receive information pertaining to children under the age of 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately obtain parental consent or otherwise delete the information from our servers. If you want to notify us of our receipt of personal information belonging to a child under the age of 13, please do so by emailing us.

Chat Rooms and Forums

This Company Website may now or in the future include web logs (i.e., blogs), chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution before disclosing your personal information via these public venues, which you do at your own risk. If you do so, you may receive, among other things, unsolicited emails or “spam” from others. Company cannot safeguard the privacy of personal information that is disclosed online in this manner.

Other Websites

When browsing this Company Website, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control. These other websites may use cookies and pixel tags, collect data, or solicit personal information. Even though Company may be affiliated with these websites, we have no control over them or how they collect, distribute or otherwise use your personal information or how they safeguard and secure your personal information. Company is not responsible or liable for the conduct, policies or actions of the owners of such websites or the content displayed on these websites. These websites are linked to this Company Website only for your convenience and you access them at your own risk.

Unsubscribing, Removing or Modifying Your Information

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. 

To modify or delete any or all of the personal information you have provided to us, please login and update your profile.

You may unsubscribe from receiving emails from us at any time by using the link included at the bottom of each email communication. You may also unsubscribe by sending us an [email](mailto:admin@youngmoney.com). 

In some limited circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Website Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement, we may retain in our files information you have requested to remove. Further, your personal information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical constraints and the fact that we back up our systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications related to this Company Website that are considered part of your account, such as technical alerts, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

Terms and Conditions

Company has a Terms and Conditions Agreement that sets forth the terms and conditions under which we provide products, services and information to you from this Company Website. Please review the terms and conditions governing your use of, and access to, this Company Website. It is your responsibility to read, understand and comply with the terms and conditions set forth therein.

Questions and Feedback

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices. Please send us [feedback](mailto:admin@youngmoney.com) pertaining to these matters or any other issue you may have with Company or this Company Website. 

If you feel that we are not following our stated Privacy Policy, you may also contact state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, your state or local consumer protection office, or The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202-FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or at [http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm.](http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm)

Last Updated: April 2, 2008
